<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>IWCS 2015</title><link href="http://iwcs2015.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://iwcs2015.github.io/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://iwcs2015.github.io/</id><updated>2015-09-13T11:11:00+01:00</updated><entry><title>Welcome</title><link href="http://iwcs2015.github.io/welcome.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-09-13T11:11:00+01:00</updated><author><name>The chairs of IWCS 2015</name></author><id>tag:iwcs2015.github.io,2015-09-13:welcome.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The 11th International Conference on Computational Semantics
(IWCS 2015) will be held at &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.qmul.ac.uk"&gt;Queen Mary University of London&lt;/a&gt;, UK on
14-17th April 2015. IWCS is the bi-yearly meeting of &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://sigsem.org"&gt;SIGSEM&lt;/a&gt;, the &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://aclweb.org"&gt;ACL&lt;/a&gt;
special interest group on semantics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="news-and-updates"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;News and Updates&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;01-Nov-2014: &lt;a class="reference external" href="/workshops-at-iwcs-2015.html"&gt;Accepted Workshops posted&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;24-Sep-2014: &lt;a class="reference external" href="/call-for-papers.html"&gt;Call for Papers available&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;13-Sep-2014: &lt;a class="reference external" href="/announcement-and-call-for-workshop-proposals.html"&gt;Call for Workshops available&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</summary></entry><entry><title>Workshops at IWCS 2015</title><link href="http://iwcs2015.github.io/workshops-at-iwcs-2015.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-11-01T11:27:00+00:00</updated><author><name>The chairs of IWCS 2015</name></author><id>tag:iwcs2015.github.io,2014-11-01:workshops-at-iwcs-2015.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;IWCS 2015 will include 5 associated workshops, held on 14th April 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="section" id="isa-11-the-11th-joint-acl-iso-workshop-on-interoperable-semantic-annotation"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a class="toc-backref" href="#id1"&gt;ISA-11: the 11th Joint ACL-ISO Workshop on Interoperable Semantic Annotation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organisers: Harry Bunt, Nancy Ide, Kiyong Lee, James Pustejovsky, Laurent Romary&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website: &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://sigsem.uvt.nl/isa11/"&gt;http://sigsem.uvt.nl/isa11/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISA-11 is the eleventh edition of a series of joint workshops of the
ACL Special Interest Group in Semantics (SIGSEM) and the International
Organization of Standards ISO. ISA-workshops bring together experts in
the annotation of semantic information as expressed in text, speech,
gestures, graphics, video, images, and in communicative behaviour
where multiple modalities are combined. Examples of semantic
annotation include the markup of events, time, space, dialogue acts,
discourse relations, semantic roles, coreference and named entities,
for which the ISO organization pursues the establishment of annotation
standards in order to support the creation of interoperable semantic
resources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="moma-models-for-modality-annotation"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a class="toc-backref" href="#id2"&gt;MOMA: Models for Modality Annotation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organisers: Malvina Nissim, Paola Pietandrea&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website: &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://malvinanissim.github.io/moma2015/"&gt;http://malvinanissim.github.io/moma2015/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The notion of modality involves a spectrum of phenomena that are
pervasive in language but far from being formalised. For an exhaustive
formalisation, a joint effort by computational, corpus, and formal
linguists as well as language typologists is required. The main aim of
this workshop is bringing together researchers from such fields,
towards the development of shared, stable annotation standards. We
believe IWCS would be an excellent venue for locating this kind of
workshop, as it has a strong tradition of bringing together linguistic
theory and implementation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="language-and-ontologies"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a class="toc-backref" href="#id3"&gt;Language and Ontologies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organisers: Roman Kutlák, Artemis Parvizi, Christina Unger&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website: &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://langandonto.github.io/"&gt;http://langandonto.github.io/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the growing importance of Semantic Web technologies, formal
ontologies are increasingly used by people with limited or no
background in formal logic, creating a significant interest in natural
and easily accessible front ends. In addition, the role of ontologies
in computational linguistics is recognised as crucial. Global interest
in these topics is witnessed by recent projects such as NeOn
(Lifecycle Support for Networked Ontologies), LEGO (Lexicon
Enhancement via the GOLD Ontology), SWAT (Semantic Web Authoring
Tool), PESCaDO (Personalized Environmental Service Configuration and
Delivery Orchestration), CO-ODE, and WhatIf (What if... questions for
Ontology Authoring).
This workshop aims to create a forum for the many ways in which
research on ontologies and research in computational linguistics
relate to each other. It aims at bringing together researchers from
different communities, including controlled languages and natural
language interfaces as well as ontology languages and linguistic
ontologies, in order to identify common interests, exploit synergies,
and share methods, tools and resources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="imc-modelling-interactive-meaning-construction-in-dialogue"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a class="toc-backref" href="#id4"&gt;IMC: Modelling Interactive Meaning Construction in Dialogue&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organisers: Ruth Kempson, Robin Cooper, Matthew Purver&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite being the mainstay of our language experience, the data of
conversational dialogue pose very considerable challenges for semantic
modelling.  They violate expectations provided by standard frameworks,
with apparently incomplete and/or highly context-dependent fragments
widespread. Conventional grammar frameworks are poorly set up to
reflect these dynamics, but the goal of defining models able to
reflect them is an active research area.  However, dialogue phenomena
and data provide us with evidence about intended and understood
meaning which can help define more suitable approaches, either through
inspection or through computational methods (especially given the
recent progress in distributional and inferential methods for deriving
semantic representations and parsers from context). This workshop
brings together researchers addressing these issues and assesses the
significance of this ongoing work both for approaches to semantics and
for computational modelling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="ads-advances-in-distributional-semantics"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a class="toc-backref" href="#id5"&gt;ADS: Advances in Distributional Semantics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organisers: Eva Maria Vecchi, Mehrnoosh Sadrzadeh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Distributional semantics is based on the idea that words that often
occur in the same context have similar meanings; this idea is
formalised using vector spaces and reasoned about using linear
algebra and statistical methods. In such models, basis vectors are
contexts and vectors represent meanings of words. Various distance
measures between the word vectors (e.g. geometric and Euclidean) are
used to reason about word similarity. Recently there has been a lot
of focus on a number of extensions: integrating machine learning
techniques (e.g. neural networks) to improve vector estimation;
compositionality of phrases and sentences; extended experimental
tasks; and extended mathematical models and algorithms. This workshop
aims to bring together researchers of the field who have answers for
the above questions, who have either advanced experience with the
experimental side of the field, or have worked on the more complex
composition operators, their ramifications, and the optimisation
techniques that would help implement them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</summary></entry><entry><title>Call for Papers</title><link href="http://iwcs2015.github.io/call-for-papers.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-09-24T18:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>Matthew Purver</name></author><id>tag:iwcs2015.github.io,2014-09-24:call-for-papers.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;11th International Conference on Computational Semantics (IWCS)
Queen Mary University of London, UK
14-17th April, 2015&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://sigsem.org/iwcs2015"&gt;http://sigsem.org/iwcs2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paper submission deadline: 16th December, 2014&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The aim of the IWCS conference is to bring together researchers interested in the computation, annotation, extraction, and representation of meaning in natural language, whether from a lexical or structural semantic perspective. IWCS embraces both symbolic and statistical approaches to computational semantics, and everything in between.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="section" id="topics-of-interest"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a class="toc-backref" href="#id1"&gt;Topics of interest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The areas of interest for the conference include all computational aspects of meaning of natural language within written, spoken, or multimodal communication. Papers are invited on topics in these and closely related areas, including the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;representation of meaning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;syntax-semantics interface&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;representing and resolving semantic ambiguity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;shallow and deep semantic processing and reasoning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;hybrid symbolic and statistical approaches to representing semantics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;alternative approaches to compositional semantics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;inference methods for computational semantics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;recognizing textual entailment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;learning by reading&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;methodologies and practices for semantic annotation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;machine learning of semantic structures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;statistical semantics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;computational aspects of lexical semantics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;semantics and ontologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;semantic web and natural language processing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;semantic aspects of language generation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;semantic relations in discourse and dialogue&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;semantics and pragmatics of dialogue acts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;multimodal and grounded approaches to computing meaning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;semantics-pragmatics interface&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="submission-requirements"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a class="toc-backref" href="#id2"&gt;Submission Requirements&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two types of submission are solicited: long papers and short papers.
Both types of papers should be submitted not later than 16th December, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Long papers should describe original research and must not exceed 10 pages. They will be published in the conference proceedings and in the ACL Anthology, and will have a full oral presentation at the conference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Short papers (typically system or project descriptions, or ongoing research) must not exceed 5 pages. They will be published in the conference proceedings and in the ACL Anthology, and will have a lightning talk at the conference, followed by a poster/demo session for discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Papers should be electronically submitted in PDF format via the START system at &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://www.softconf.com/iwcs2015/"&gt;https://www.softconf.com/iwcs2015/&lt;/a&gt;. Please contact the organisers if you have problems using START.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please follow the information for authors for instructions on formatting your paper, given on the conference webpage
&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://sigsem.org/iwcs2015/"&gt;http://sigsem.org/iwcs2015/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="program-chairs"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a class="toc-backref" href="#id3"&gt;Program Chairs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Matthew Purver, Queen Mary University of London
Mehrnoosh Sadrzadeh, Queen Mary University of London
Matthew Stone, Rutgers University&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="program-committee"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a class="toc-backref" href="#id4"&gt;Program Committee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TBD&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="important-dates"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a class="toc-backref" href="#id5"&gt;Important dates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;16 December 2014&lt;/strong&gt;  Paper submissions due (long and short)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;02 February 2015&lt;/strong&gt;  Notification of acceptance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;25 February 2015&lt;/strong&gt;  Final camera-ready papers due&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;14 April 2015&lt;/strong&gt;     IWCS workshops&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;15-17 April 2015&lt;/strong&gt;  Main IWCS conference&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</summary><category term="call"></category></entry><entry><title>Announcement and call for workshop proposals</title><link href="http://iwcs2015.github.io/announcement-and-call-for-workshop-proposals.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-09-13T11:11:00+01:00</updated><author><name>The chairs of IWCS 2015</name></author><id>tag:iwcs2015.github.io,2014-09-13:announcement-and-call-for-workshop-proposals.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;11th International Conference on Computational Semantics (IWCS)
Queen Mary University of London, UK
14-17th April 2015 (workshops on 14th)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Proposal deadline: 10th October 2014&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The International Conference for Computational Semantics (IWCS) invites proposals for one-day or half-day workshops, to be held in conjunction with the 2015 IWCS conference. IWCS 2015 will take place on 15th-17th April 2015 at Queen Mary University of London, UK. Workshops will take place on the day immediately preceding the conference: 14th April 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The aim of the IWCS conference is to bring together researchers interested in any aspects of the computation, annotation, extraction, and representation of meaning in natural language, whether this is from a lexical or structural semantic perspective. IWCS embraces both symbolic and statistical approaches to computational semantics, and everything in between.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="section" id="topics-of-interest"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a class="toc-backref" href="#id1"&gt;Topics of interest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Topics of interest for the workshops include all those topics relevant to the main conference, including but not limited to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;representation of meaning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;syntax-semantics interface&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;representing and resolving semantic ambiguity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;shallow and deep semantic processing and reasoning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;hybrid symbolic and statistical approaches to representing semantics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;alternative approaches to compositional semantics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;inference methods for computational semantics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;recognizing textual entailment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;learning by reading&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;methodologies and practices for semantic annotation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;machine learning of semantic structures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;statistical semantics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;computational aspects of lexical semantics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;semantics and ontologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;semantic web and natural language processing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;semantic aspects of language generation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;semantic relations in discourse and dialogue&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;semantics and pragmatics of dialogue acts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;multimodal and grounded approaches to computing meaning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;semantics-pragmatics interface&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="submission-information"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a class="toc-backref" href="#id2"&gt;Submission information&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Proposals for workshops should contain:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A title and brief (2-page max) description of the workshop topic and content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An estimate of the audience size&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The names, postal addresses, and email addresses of the organizers, with one-paragraph statements of their research interests and areas of expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A list of potential members of the program committee, with an indication of which members have already agreed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A description of special requirements for technical needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Proposals should be submitted by email to&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;a class="reference external" href="mailto:iwcs2015@gmail.com"&gt;iwcs2015@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;as soon as possible, but no later than 10th October 2014.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Notification of acceptance of workshop proposals will occur no later than 17th October 2014.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="after-acceptance"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a class="toc-backref" href="#id3"&gt;After acceptance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organizers of accepted workshops must provide descriptions of their workshops, for inclusion in the conference registration material, by 1st December 2014. The description must be provided in two formats: an ASCII version that can be included with the email announcement, and an HTML version that can be included on the conference home page. These descriptions should be mailed to: &lt;a class="reference external" href="mailto:iwcs2015@gmail.com"&gt;iwcs2015@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The final workshop materials must be received by the IWCS organizers by 1st March 2015. This includes the detailed proceedings (camera-ready versions of papers), which will be made available electronically, as well as a short workshop program, which will be printed together with the main conference program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="finances"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a class="toc-backref" href="#id4"&gt;Finances&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Workshops must be financially self-supporting. The conference organizers will establish registration rates so as to provide the room, audio-visual equipment, internet access, snacks for breaks, and the workshop proceedings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="important-dates"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a class="toc-backref" href="#id5"&gt;Important dates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10th October 2014&lt;/strong&gt; Workshop proposal submissions due&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;17th October 2014&lt;/strong&gt; Workshop proposal notification of acceptance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1st December 2014&lt;/strong&gt; Workshop description mailed to IWCS organizers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1st March 201&lt;/strong&gt; Workshop material due to IWCS organizers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;14th April 2015&lt;/strong&gt; Workshop date&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</summary></entry><entry><title>Instructions for Authors</title><link href="http://iwcs2015.github.io/instructions-for-authors.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-09-01T19:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>Matthew Purver</name></author><id>tag:iwcs2015.github.io,2014-09-01:instructions-for-authors.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;div class="section" id="formatting-instructions"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Formatting Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Papers should be formatted with a Times font, size 11pt, typeset in one column, and with margins of 25mm all around. Papers should be submitted in PDF A4 paper format using the START electronic submission web page at &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://www.softconf.com/iwcs2015/main"&gt;https://www.softconf.com/iwcs2015/main&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;strong&gt;Note that submissions must be anonymous.&lt;/strong&gt; Long paper submissions should not exceed 10 pages plus an additional page for references. Short paper submissions should not exceed 5 pages plus an additional page for references. The first page should include an abstract of c. 10 lines. Authors are strongly encouraged to prepare their submission using LaTeX.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="latex-submissions"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;LaTeX Submissions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Users of LaTeX should use documentclass &lt;tt class="docutils literal"&gt;article&lt;/tt&gt; with the options &lt;tt class="docutils literal"&gt;a4paper&lt;/tt&gt; and &lt;tt class="docutils literal"&gt;11pt&lt;/tt&gt;, using the packages &lt;tt class="docutils literal"&gt;times&lt;/tt&gt; and &lt;tt class="docutils literal"&gt;geometry&lt;/tt&gt; to set font and margins. For citations please use the &lt;tt class="docutils literal"&gt;natbib&lt;/tt&gt; package with &lt;tt class="docutils literal"&gt;chicago.bst&lt;/tt&gt; as bibliography style. See below for an example LaTeX file:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span class="k"&gt;\documentclass&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="na"&gt;[a4paper,11pt]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;article&lt;span class="nb"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class="k"&gt;\usepackage&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;graphicx&lt;span class="nb"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;span class="c"&gt;%%% for including graphics&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="k"&gt;\usepackage&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;url&lt;span class="nb"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;       &lt;span class="c"&gt;%%% for including URLs&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="k"&gt;\usepackage&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;times&lt;span class="nb"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="k"&gt;\usepackage&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;natbib&lt;span class="nb"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="k"&gt;\usepackage&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="na"&gt;[margin=25mm]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;geometry&lt;span class="nb"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class="k"&gt;\title&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;Example Paper for IWCS&lt;span class="nb"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="k"&gt;\date&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;{}&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class="k"&gt;\author&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;Example Author&lt;span class="k"&gt;\\&lt;/span&gt;
       Affiliation&lt;span class="k"&gt;\\&lt;/span&gt;
       &lt;span class="k"&gt;\texttt&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;example@email.org&lt;span class="nb"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class="k"&gt;\and&lt;/span&gt; Someone Else&lt;span class="k"&gt;\\&lt;/span&gt;
       Another Affiliation&lt;span class="k"&gt;\\&lt;/span&gt;
       &lt;span class="k"&gt;\texttt&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;another@email.org&lt;span class="nb"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="nb"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class="k"&gt;\begin&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;document&lt;span class="nb"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="k"&gt;\maketitle&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="k"&gt;\thispagestyle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;empty&lt;span class="nb"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="k"&gt;\pagestyle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;empty&lt;span class="nb"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class="k"&gt;\section&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;Introduction&lt;span class="nb"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;

....

&lt;span class="k"&gt;\bibliographystyle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;chicago&lt;span class="nb"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="k"&gt;\bibliography&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;mybib&lt;span class="nb"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class="k"&gt;\end&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nb"&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;document&lt;span class="nb"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</summary><category term="instructions"></category></entry><entry><title>Organisation</title><link href="http://iwcs2015.github.io/organisation.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-09-01T18:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>Matthew Purver</name></author><id>tag:iwcs2015.github.io,2014-09-01:organisation.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;div class="section" id="conference-chairs"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Conference Chairs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;dl class="docutils"&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;Matthew Purver&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Queen Mary University of London&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;Mehrnoosh Sadrzadeh&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Queen Mary University of London&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;Matthew Stone&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Rutgers University&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="local-organisation"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Local Organisation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="local-chairs"&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Local Chairs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Matthew Purver&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mehrnoosh Sadrzadeh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="website"&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Website&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dmitrijs Milajevs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="programme-committee"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Programme Committee&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TBA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</summary><category term="organisation"></category></entry></feed>