<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>IWCS 2015</title><link href="http://iwcs2015.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://iwcs2015.github.io/feeds/hackathon.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://iwcs2015.github.io/</id><updated>2015-02-03T13:32:00+00:00</updated><entry><title>Hackathon</title><link href="http://iwcs2015.github.io/hackathon.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-02-03T13:32:00+00:00</updated><author><name>The chairs of IWCS 2015</name></author><id>tag:iwcs2015.github.io,2015-02-03:hackathon.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;!-- :news_headline: Hackathon announcement --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We invite researchers, developers students and users of semantic NLP tools to
participate at the Hackathon. The event will take place on &lt;strong&gt;April 18th-19th&lt;/strong&gt;
in London, UK.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The goal of the event is to provide an opportunity to discuss and develop tools
that are used in Computational Semantics. Moreover, we also would like to
attract anyone interested in data processing tools so they could contribute to
open source projects represented at the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hackathon is organised by the computational linguistic lab at
QMUL and sponsored by the &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.epsrc.ac.uk/"&gt;EPSRC&lt;/a&gt; grant &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://gow.epsrc.ac.uk/NGBOViewGrant.aspx?GrantRef=EP/J002607/1"&gt;EP/J002607/1&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="section" id="project-ideas"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a class="toc-backref" href="#id8"&gt;Project ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="tweet-paraphrase-generator"&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a class="toc-backref" href="#id9"&gt;Tweet paraphrase generator&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Given a tweet, the system has to come up with a paraphrase. For example, by
substituting all the content words (nouns, verbs, adjectives and adverbs) with
similar words.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A twitter bot should monitor Twitter for tweets that contain &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23iwcs"&gt;#iwcs&lt;/a&gt; and generate a paraphrase tweet. Also,
tweets directed to the bot should be replied with a paraphrase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="nltk-corpus-readers"&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a class="toc-backref" href="#id10"&gt;NLTK corpus readers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.nltk.org/"&gt;NLTK&lt;/a&gt; is a natural language toolkit that provides basic tools to deal with
textual information. &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.nltk.org/api/nltk.corpus.reader.html#module-nltk.corpus.reader"&gt;Corpus readers&lt;/a&gt; are interfaces to access textual resources
(called corpora). The task is to provide interfaces to the following resources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="groningen-meaning-bank"&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Groningen Meaning Bank&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://gmb.let.rug.nl/"&gt;Groningen meaning bank&lt;/a&gt; is a free semantically annotated corpus that anyone
can edit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="ukwac"&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;UkWaC&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://wacky.sslmit.unibo.it/doku.php"&gt;UkWaC&lt;/a&gt; is a 2 billion word corpus constructed from the Web limiting the crawl
to the .uk domain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="wikipedia"&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Wikipedia&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wikipedia provides &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://dumps.wikimedia.org/enwiki/"&gt;dumps&lt;/a&gt; of all its content. However, to be used as a corpus a
dump has to be cleaned up from the wiki markup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="amr"&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;AMR&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://amr.isi.edu/index.html"&gt;AMR Bank&lt;/a&gt; is a set of English sentences paired with simple, readable semantic
representations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="call-for-sponsorship"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a class="toc-backref" href="#id11"&gt;Call for Sponsorship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IWCS is the International Conference in Computational Semantics series: the bi-yearly
meeting of SIGSEM, the ACL special interest group on semantics. The areas
of interest for the conference include all computational aspects of meaning of
natural language within written, spoken, or multimodal communication. We are
organising the 11th IWCS conference; this will be held in Queen Mary University
of London on April 14-17th 2015. For more info see &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://sigsem.org/iwcs2015"&gt;http://sigsem.org/iwcs2015&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year we would like to organize a hackathon right after the conference on
April 18th-19th. The goal of the event is to provide an opportunity to
discuss and develop tools that are used in Computational Semantics. Moreover, we
also would like to attract anyone interested in data processing tools so they
could contribute to open source projects represented at the event. Currently, we
are looking for sponsors to support the event. We aim to invite core developers
of relevant open source projects (e.g. &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.nltk.org/"&gt;NLTK&lt;/a&gt; and
&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://scikit-learn.org/"&gt;scikit- learn&lt;/a&gt;) and provide travel grants to
everyone interested to attend the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are also looking for experienced developers who can mentor participants and
assist with software engineering tools (version control systems, editor,
development environment set up and so on).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To support the event you could:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide funding to cover catering, traveling and organisational costs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Propose project ideas that might be implemented during the hackathon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Invite experienced developers to mentor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share relevant datasets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In return we can:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on your project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Put your logo on the hackathon web page &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://iwcs2015.githib.io/hackathon"&gt;http://iwcs2015.githib.io/hackathon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide a space for a poster, promotional material, an information desk, etc.
at the venue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="contact-information"&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a class="toc-backref" href="#id12"&gt;Contact information&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In case you are interested in supporting the event contact Dmitrijs Milajevs
&amp;lt;&lt;a class="reference external" href="mailto:d.milajevs@qmul.ac.uk"&gt;d.milajevs@qmul.ac.uk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</summary></entry></feed>