<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>IWCS 2015</title><link href="http://iwcs2015.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://iwcs2015.github.io/feeds/open-space.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://iwcs2015.github.io/</id><updated>2015-03-11T22:16:00+00:00</updated><entry><title>Open Space</title><link href="http://iwcs2015.github.io/openspace.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-03-11T22:16:00+00:00</updated><author><name>The chairs of IWCS 2015</name></author><id>tag:iwcs2015.github.io,2015-03-11:openspace.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;!-- .. contents::
    :depth: 1 --&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="open-space-unconference"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Open Space / Unconference&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Following a successful session at &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.ling.uni-potsdam.de/iwcs2013/"&gt;IWCS 2013&lt;/a&gt;, we plan to set most of Thursday
afternoon aside for an Open Space workshop (aka &amp;quot;unconference&amp;quot;). The goal of
this event is to allow participants to discuss any topic in computational
semantics they are passionate about, in small groups of people who care about
the same topic. Open Space events are self-organized: topics are proposed by
participants, sessions are run by participants, and all the conference
organizers do is facilitate the process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Open Space event will be structured as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Thursday at 15:30, we'll meet in the David Sizer Lecture Theatre (ground
floor, behind the registration desk). After a brief introduction to the Open
Space format, anyone can get up and propose a topic for a session that they
would like to happen that afternoon. This topic can be anything you like; it
could be as specific as your favorite theory of scope ambiguity, as general as
how to reconcile logic-based and distributional semantics, or even something
that usually has no place at conferences (computational semantics education?
ideas for shared tasks?). The only requirement is that you would enjoy talking
about this topic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;People will then show their preference for particular topics by&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sessions will be organized into time slots; depending on the number and
interdependency of topics, probably 3 slots starting at 16:00, 16:40 and
17:20. During each time slot, everyone who is interested in a topic is welcome
to join the session. The crucial rule we will follow is the &amp;quot;Law of Two Feet&amp;quot;:
If you find that you are not learning anything and not contributing anything,
you are encouraged to get up and leave the room. In this particular context,
this is not a sign of impoliteness; it is a way of maximizing the time you're
spending in a place that you enjoy, and of ensuring that everyone who remains
in the session can be certain that everyone who is there is having a good
time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Throughout the afternoon, we will keep a coffee break area open. If there is
no session going on that you find interesting, you are welcome to hang out in
the coffee corner. If you left your session, you can go there to refresh
yourself, and perhaps join some other session. The key goal is that you enjoy
yourself and feel that you're participating in discussions that you care
about. Whether these happen in your original session, or some other session
that you join, or just while you're hanging out having coffee -- that's all
good.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The final sessions will need to finish promptly at 18:00 -- we'll need to
set off for central London to catch the boat for dinner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We have set up &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/iwcs2015/iwcs2015.github.io/wiki"&gt;a Wiki for use during the conference&lt;/a&gt; - you need a Github
account to edit it, so just sign up for one if you don't already have one. You
are welcome and encouraged to take a few minutes at the end of your session to
summarize it in a Wiki article. If you feel uncomfortable sharing your
discussion, you are of course not required to do this. After the conference,
we will take the Wiki offline and distribute a reader with all articles to all
participants.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find more information on Open Space in general in its &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Open_Space_Technology"&gt;Wikipedia page&lt;/a&gt; and in the &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.openspaceworld.com/users_guide.htm"&gt;Open Space
user's guide&lt;/a&gt;. A brief video
introduction is &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aD3S0wlbek0"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</summary></entry></feed>